[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":110521,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":198946,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":24283,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":223232,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":13279,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":236514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2366,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":238881,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":7832,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":246714,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1382,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":248097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get yo ur resul t.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":10576,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":258674,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":8111,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":266786,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6172,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":272959,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1  = 2 bec ause 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1265,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":274226,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5255,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":279484,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1333,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":280819,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with  the firs t number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5935,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":286755,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1382,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":288139,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":5471,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":293611,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1527,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":295139,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4311,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":299451,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1079,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":300532,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4768,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":305300,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1342,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":306643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger,  you sub tract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3812,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":310456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1315,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":311772,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":46415,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":358191,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":61878,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":420072,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":121980,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":542054,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3453,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":545510,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":26736,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":572247,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2503,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":574751,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is  the inv erse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4071,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":578823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1367,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":580191,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2975,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":583167,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1318,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":584487,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":5264,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":589751,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":12008,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":601760,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":56317,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":658078,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>.  <br />< br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":82530,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":740612,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":12345,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":752959,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":7379,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":760339,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":50285,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":810626,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":68744,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":879373,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a gener ator und er +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":41556,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":920932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":6059,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":926993,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":6613,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":933607,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":3310,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":936918,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the re maining  questions as accurately as possible.","rt":31320,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":968239,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":7351,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":975592,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":2071,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":977664,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4328,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":981993,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"f ree","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4476,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":986472,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4222,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":990696,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3974,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":994672,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3600,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":998275,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I added 4 and 1 to get 5.  Because 5 is smaller than 9, I won't be subtracting the number from 9.","response_history":["I added 1","I added 4 and o","I added 4 and 1 to get 5.  Because 5 is smaller than 9, I won't be subtracting the number from 9."],"rt":59062,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1057339,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3   I added 8 and 4 to get 12.  Because 12 is larger than 9, I subtract 9 and that leaves with me 3.","response_history":["3   I added 8 and 4 yo","3   I added 8 and 4 y","3   I added 8 and 4 to get 12.  I","3   I added  8 and 4  to get 12.  Because 12 i ","3   I added 8 and 4 to get 12.  Because 12 is larger than 9, I subtract 9 and that leaves with me 3."],"rt":41515,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1098857,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"The identity under 9 is zero like it is with +6.  If there is a number that is equal to 9 after adding the two numbers and subtracting 9, you end up with 0.","response_history":["The identity under 9 is zeor","The identity under 9 is zeo","The identity under 9 is zero like it is with +6.  If there is a number than","The identity under 9 is zero like it is with +6.  If there is a number that is equal to 9 after adding the two numbers and subtracting 9, you end up with 0."],"rt":58926,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1157786,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":15633,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1173424,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":3415,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1176840,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":6162,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1183004,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 un der +<su b>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6  When I add 6 to 3 I get 9.  I then subtract 9 and end up with 0.  6 is the number that is added to 3 to end up with the inverse.","response_history":["T","6  when","6  whe","6  wh","6  w","6  When I add 6 6","6  When I add 6 to 3 I get 9.  I then subtract 9 givi","6  When I add 6 to 3 I get 9.  I then subtract 9 giv","6  When I add 6 to 3 I get 9.  I then subtract 9 gi","6  When I add 6 to 3 I get 9.  I then subtract 9 g","6  When I add 6 to 3 I get 9.  I then subtract 9 and end up with z","6  When I add 6 to 3 I get 9.  I then subtract 9 and end up with 0.  0 is the inv","6  When I add 6 to 3 I get 9.  I then subtract 9 and end up with 0.  0 is t","6  When I add 6 to 3 I get 9.  I then subtract 9 and end up with 0.  6 is the number that is added to 3 to end up with the inverse ","6  When I add 6 to 3 I get 9.  I then subtract 9 and e nd up wi th 0.  6 is the number that is added to 3 to end up with the inverse."],"rt":139165,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1322171,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.  Because 2 when added with  other even numbers won't give you 9 and allow you to get to its identity.","response_history":["No.  I think if you end up adding other numbers to 2, ","No.  I think if you end up a","No.  I think if you end up ","I don't think so.  I'm not sure.  ","No.  Because 2 when added with  other even numbers won't give you 9 and allow you to get to its identity."],"rt":179562,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1501737,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you g ot your  answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I think so.  Adding 3 with +9 each time allows you to end up with 9, subtract 9 from that, and get the identity.","response_history":["I think so.  Adding 3 with +9 each time allows t","I think so.  Adding 3 with +9 each time allows you to end up with 9, subtract 9 from that, and get the identiy","I think so.  Adding 3 with +9 each time allows you to end up with 9, subtract 9 from that, and get the identity."],"rt":38479,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1540218,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, I don't think it is mainly because once it's added to another 5, you're unable to make the smaller numbers.","response_history":["No, I don't think it is becaue","No, I don' t think  it is because ","No, I don't think it is mainly because once it's added toge","No, I don't think it is mainly because once it's added tog","No, I don't think it is mainly because once it's added to","No, I don't think it is mainly because once it's added t","No, I don't think it is mainly because once it's added to another 5, you're unable to make the smalelr n","No, I don't think it is mainly because once it's added to another 5, you're unable to make the smalelr ","No, I don't think it is mainly because once it's added to another 5, you're unable to make the smalelr","No, I don't think it is mainly because once it's added to another 5, you're unable to make the smalel","No, I don't think it is mainly because once it's added to another 5, you're unable to make the smale","No, I don't think it is mainly because once it's added to another 5, you're unable to make the smaller numbers."],"rt":68285,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1608506,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I think the same applies to 6, where you won't be able to create the smaller numbers with it.  I'm not completely sure though.","response_history":["I think the same applies to 6, where you won't be able to create the sa","I think the same applies to 6, where you won't be able to create the smaller numbers, ","I think the same applies to 6, where you won't be able to create the smaller numbers,","I think the same applies to 6, where you won't be able to create the smaller numbers with it.  I'm not completely sure thought","I think the same applies to 6, where you won't be able to create the smaller numbers with it.  I'm not completely sure though."],"rt":39386,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1647894,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":46940,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1694837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 + 1 +1n","response_history":["1 + 1 +n","1 + 1 +1n"],"rt":46600,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1741439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x +n x  I added x to get an amount higher or equal to x.  So x is the number that makes that possible.","response_history":["x + ","x +n x  I addd","x +n x  I added x to get an amount higher or equal to x and subtract thea","x +n x  I added x to get an amount higher or equal to x and subtract the","x +n x  I added x to get an amount higher or equal to x and subtract that t","x +n x  I added x to get an amount higher or equal to x and subtract that nu","x +n x  I added x to get an amount higher or equal to x.  So x is the number that makes that possible."],"rt":79060,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1820501,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":" ","response":"I don't how you would find out whether there was a pattern.  I was relying on seeing the numbers involved, so I'm not sure.","response_history":["I don't how you would b","I don't how you would find out whether there was a pattern.  I was relying on seeing the h","I don't how you would find out whether there was a pattern.  I was relying on seeing the numbers involved, so I'm not sure."],"rt":97731,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1918235,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":9659,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1927898,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["False","True"],"rt":16346,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1944246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["True","False"],"rt":15446,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1959694,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"Because in order to end up with an identity, you have to  be able  to reach the equivalent number.","response_history":["Because in order to end up with an indentity, you ","Because in order to end up with an identity o","Because in order to end up with an identity ","Because in order to end up with an identity, you hae ","Because in order to end up with an identity, you hae","Because in order to end up with an identity, you have to be able to reach te ","Because in order to end up with an identity, you have to be able to reach te","Because in order to end up with an identity, you have to be able to reach the q","Because in order to end up with an identity, you have to be able to reach the equivalent number."],"rt":71317,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2031012,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes ","Never "],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":10221,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2041236,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I'm stumped on this one.  I think it is part of the time depending whether the number is odd or even.","response_history":["Im st","Im s","Im ","Im","I","I'm stumped on this one.  I think it is part of the time depending whether the nuber","I'm stumped on this one.  I think it is part of the time depending whether the nube","I'm stumped on this one.  I think it is part of the time depending whether the nub","I'm stumped on this one.  I think it is part of the time depen ding whe ther the number is odd or even."],"rt":31848,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2073086,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":12069,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2085158,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1822,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2086982,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"43","response_history":["43"],"rt":2727,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2089710,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":3895,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2093606,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The most advanced class was a basic college level math course.","response_history":["The most advanced class was a basi c colleg e level math course."],"rt":22369,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2115976,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":5401,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2121379,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or rec ently"," 5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4484,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2125863,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":7235,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2133099,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3220,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2136320,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2728,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2139048,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2566,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2141616,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2146384,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.","response_history":["No."],"rt":4503,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2150888,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I enjoyed it.  It felt much more intuitive in the beginning, then started to feel much more challenging.","response_history":["I enjoyed it.  I don't know how ","I enjoyed it.  I ","I enjoyed it.  I was ","I enjoyed it.  I was","I enjoyed it.  I wa","I enjoyed it.  I w","I enjoyed it.  I ","I enjoyed it.  It felt much more intuitive in the beginning, then started to fel","I enjoyed it.  It felt much more intuitive in the beginning, then started to feel much more challenging."],"rt":32871,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2183760,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]